<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Real Estate Raw Show</title>
    <description>Our mission at Katcam Real Estate is to be your best resource for San Diego real estate advice. Whether you are a buyer, seller, or investor, our team of professionals can answer any questions you might have about real estate. If you are looking to buy or sell a home, you can get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from The Katcam Real Estate, your professional San Diego Real Estate Agents.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2018 13:09:45 -0600</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2018 13:09:45 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.7.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>What Will YOU DO with $50,000 to $250,000 in Cash Credit?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/q3IouwKT5Q0?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Welcome back to the Real Estate Raw Show! On this very special episode, we’re joined by Fund&amp;amp;Grow COO Mike Banks. Fund&amp;amp;Grow is a corporation specializing in financial and strategic advisory services, and Michael has sat down with us for an interview today to discuss the benefits of working with his company.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cited below for your convenience are timestamps that will direct you to various points in the interview. Feel free to watch the full message or use these timestamps to browse specific topics at your leisure:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;0:52 - How (and why) Fund&amp;amp;Grow helps people obtain zero-interest business credit lines&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2:51 - What kind of qualifications does a person need to apply for funding through Fund&amp;amp;Grow?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;6:18 - The benefit of working through Fund&amp;amp;Grow as opposed to seeking funding on your own&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;7:54 - Why “OPM” (other people’s money) is a great resource for those entering real estate investing&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;8:14 - How Mike got into this business&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;10:18 - The difference between hard-money loans and the funds available through Fund&amp;amp;Grow&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;11:01 - How working with Fund&amp;amp;Grow works&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;15:54 - A word from our sponsors&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;18:37 - Why you should apply with Fund&amp;amp;Grow today&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;19:03 - What happens at the end of an investor’s term with Fund&amp;amp;Grow?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;22:43 - Explaining the “rinse and repeat” opportunities available by using Fund&amp;amp;Grow&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;27:20 - What Fund&amp;amp;Grow can offer to people with limited personal credit&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;29:27 - What to do if you’re ready to get started with Fund&amp;amp;Grow or if you would like more information&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;31:04 - Are there limits to how you can use money from Fund&amp;amp;Grow?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Want low interest funding for your Business or Real Estate Deals? Click the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fundandgrow.com/prequalification?t=p&amp;amp;joemendoza&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Fund&amp;amp;Grow link &lt;/a&gt;on the side of my blog!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can also learn more here: &lt;a href=&quot;http://qwikcash.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;http://qwikcash.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any other questions or would like more information, feel free to give us a call or send us an email. We look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Dec 2018 15:22:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/what-will-you-do-with-50000-to-250000-in-cash-credit.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/what-will-you-do-with-50000-to-250000-in-cash-credit.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Making an Impact Through Commercial Investing</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/GH62HZg_JxE?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Welcome back to another edition of the Real Estate Raw Show. This time, our special guest happens to be expert commercial broker Terry Moore—who has done over 400 transactions and is a CCIM (Certified Commercial Investment Member), which is one of the most elite designations available in the real estate industry. &lt;strong&gt;As always, I’ve included timestamps below so that you can navigate the discussion at your leisure:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;0:30 - An introduction to Terry Moore&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;0:55 - Terry explains his and his team’s calling&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1:25 - Terry’s perspective on our current market from a commercial investing perspective&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3:50 - Touching on the shortage of commercial properties in San Diego County&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;7:05 - Terry gauges the window of opportunity for commercial investment in San Diego County&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;8:25 - How much new investors should plan to spend (and earn) per unit&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;12:01 - How San Diego County compares in terms of investment opportunities to other areas of the country&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;15:01 - A word from our sponsors&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;18:00 - Why investing in California is worthwhile&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;22:37 - The value of investing in supply-constrained markets&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;26:23 - Terry talks about his book “Building Legacy Wealth”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;27:17 - Terry explains the four stages of learning and how he helps investors succeed at any stage&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;29:17 - Why legacy matters as an investor&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;30:19 - What inspired Terry to write his book&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;32:24 - How to contact Terry Moore&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any other questions or would like more information, feel free to give me a call or send me an email. We look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2018 13:51:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/making-an-impact-through-commercial-investing.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/making-an-impact-through-commercial-investing.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Ins and Outs of the Note-Buying Industry</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/fQ9VmoGNMPc?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve known Scott for a few years, and he’s a stand-up guy doing great business. I’m so pleased to have him on “The Real Estate Raw Show” to talk about his career and his tactics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;For your convenience, I’ve provided timestamps below so that you can navigate the conversation Scott and I had at your leisure:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1:25—The sudden and drastic downturn of the market in 2008 that caused Scott to leave the mortgage industry to turn to buying distressed debt&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2:10—What exactly does it mean to buy notes?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;5:30—What is the best time of year to buy notes, or is it year-round?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;9:40—Scott’s words of caution to anyone out there teaching about note-buying&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;11:20—For those just getting started in the business, what is the hardest aspect of the job?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;13:00—Different states have different foreclosure time frames, so are some states easier to work in than others?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;14:15—Start-up fees and ongoing monthly fees for new arrivals to the field&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;17:00—A quick break in the discussion and a word from our sponsors&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;20:33—What kind of numbers are in play in the note-buying game?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;25:00—What to say in tough situations involving tenants of the properties&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;28:30—The market is shifting; inventory is staying on longer and prices are coming down. What impact does that have in this business?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;32:00—Scott’s preferences among asset class, storage, apartments, shopping centers, single-family homes&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;34:25—Is negotiating with the banks difficult?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;35:45—Is there a minimum buy-in?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I really appreciate Scott spending time on our show today to share his words of wisdom. If you’d like to speak with Scott about buying notes or any aspect of his business, he can be reached at (512) 585-3810 by phone or at &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:Scott@weclosenotes.com&quot;&gt;Scott@weclosenotes.com &lt;/a&gt;by email. You can also visit his website at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.WeCloseNotes.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;www.WeCloseNotes.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For any questions you have for me, you are always encouraged to reach out to me. I hope to hear from you soon!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 14:41:18 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/the-ins-and-outs-of-the-note-buying-industry.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/the-ins-and-outs-of-the-note-buying-industry.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dave Sanchez talks about Value Add Plays</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/2-hUw_tT3iM?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During my most recent episode of the Real Estate Raw Show, I brought on another very special guest: Dave Sanchez, an investor who has accumulated more than 800 units. I only met Dave recently, but I knew shortly after having been introduced to him that I wanted to bring him on for a conversation about his success and about investing in general.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cited below for your convenience are timestamps that will direct you to various points in the interview. Feel free to watch the full message or use these timestamps to browse specific topics at your leisure:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1:09 - Dave tells the story of how he got to where he is today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;7:21 - Explaining a few differences between multi-unit and single-family investment properties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;8:31 - Dave explains where he likes to invest and why.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;9:31 - Dave explains different classes of investment properties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;12:20 - Dave explains what a syndication is as it relates to real estate investing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;15:26 - A word from our sponsors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;18:42 - Dave explains what he’s working on right now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;21:35 - Dave’s advice for rookie investors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;25:09 - Why real estate investing is a “team sport.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;29:07 - Why you need to have a solid “player” on your investing “team.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;30:08 - Some final words of advice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any other questions or would like more information, feel free to give us a call or send us an email. We look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 11:13:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/dave-sanchez-talks-about-value-add-plays.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/dave-sanchez-talks-about-value-add-plays.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>My Interview With the “Systems Guru”: Vinney Chopra</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/wswyCQCa_os?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I first heard Vinney on a podcast in which he was talking about how he came to this country with only $7. From there, he accumulated property after property after property, and he now has a youth academy focused on 18-year-olds and is managing over $200 million worth of multifamily units.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today, I wanted to speak with Vinney and hear his story because it’s chock-full of value and wisdom. To learn his story, methods, and strategies, refer to the video above. I’ve included timestamps below so that you can navigate the discussion at your leisure:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1:15—Vinney’s modest upbringing and journey to America with only $7&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2:50—Going from an engineer to a salesperson&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;6:25—From student to teacher: Training and coaching about multifamily sales&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;8:28—How to pivot from single-family real estate to multifamily&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;10:28—Vinney’s deal-finding techniques&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;13:52—Expanding his reach to marketplaces across the country&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;16:55—What is an offering memorandum?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;18:00—A short break and a word from our sponsors&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;21:34—Back to our show!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;22:19—Vinney’s biggest “why”: What kept him going through the hard times&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;27:14—How much time Vinny spends finding or raising money versus finding a deal&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;28:37—Advice for single-family agents about our turning market: Should we be cautious or carefree?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;32:38—Wrapping up his previous company and meeting in the middle: How he manages to operate as CEO when his marketplaces are all over the country&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;33:38—Vinney’s Youth Academy; his advice for those just starting&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;36:56—Vinney’s family; Moneil Management Group, one of his companies, is named after both his children&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;38:16—Vinney’s parting words; an invitation to reach out to him&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m so grateful to have had Vinney Chopra on my show. He is a fountain of wisdom and knowledge about multifamily syndication and so much more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To reach Vinney and his team, text the word “Syndication” to 474747. He believes in prompt communication, so you can expect a reply shortly after. After he has collected your email address and contact information, he can offer a range of free things, including a sampling of his courses. Additionally, you can visit his website at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.VinneyChopra.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;www.VinneyChopra.com&lt;/a&gt; to see all his podcasts, interviews, techniques, and more.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Vinney also likes to blog on the BiggerPockets website, where his content has gotten him named Editor’s Choice for the last three or four months. To read his blogs, visit &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.biggerpockets.com/users/vchopra&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://www.biggerpockets.com/users/vchopra&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have any questions for me, you are always encouraged to reach out to me and my team at Katcam Real Estate. We’d love to hear from you.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 14:40:13 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/my-interview-with-the-systems-guru-vinney-chopra.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/my-interview-with-the-systems-guru-vinney-chopra.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Real Estate Raw: Cole Realty Resource</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/y-0o61XG6ag?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the latest episode of “Real Estate Raw,” I had the pleasure of being joined by Tyler Steenken from Cole Realty Resource. I talk to a lot of people around the country who are in the real estate business and one of the biggest challenges they have is lead generation. They don’t know who to call. That’s where Tyler and Cole Realty Resource come in—by providing data and information to help small businesses, investors, and more. &lt;strong&gt;Here’s an outline of our wide-ranging discussion, with timestamps to that you can skip ahead to the part(s) that interest you the most:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1:05- A closer look at the data and information that Tyler provides to his clients.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3:10- Why this system from Cole Realty Resource is the perfect way to find the people you’re looking for with ease.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4:40- How you can marry this service with Sly Broadcasting to increase your results.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;6:30- A prospecting tip that I teach to every one of my coaching clients.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;8:40- A personal success story from my experience with Cole Realty Resource.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;13:50- How to leverage the information you get from Cole Realty Resource to use for an open house.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;17:30- The major benefits investors can see from Cole Realty Resource’s data&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;19:20- How data helps you compete strongly in the contact sport of real estate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;21:05- How to get started in the process of working with Cole Realty Resource with a special offer from this show.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;22:10- Final thoughts from Tyler.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks again to Tyler for taking the time to join me on this episode. If you have any questions for Tyler in the meantime, feel free to give him a call at (800) 800-3271. &lt;strong&gt;Be sure to mention I heard it through “Joe Mendoza” for VIP service and discounts!  &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any other questions for me, don’t hesitate to reach out by giving me a call or sending me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 08:30:27 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/real-estate-raw-cole-realty-resource.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/real-estate-raw-cole-realty-resource.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Retire in 3 to 5 Years By Investing in Multi-Family Property</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/K-iruTIndnQ?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Welcome back to another episode of “Real Estate Raw.” Michael Blank is today’s guest, and he’s an absolute guru when it comes to real estate investing–specifically, investing in multi-family property.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In our discussion we cover a variety of important topics, so once again I’ve provided timestamps of the video above so you can jump ahead to the section(s) that interest you the most:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;0:49—How Michael got into multi-family property investing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2:57—How a person can retire in three to five years by investing in multi-family units.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4:45—How to calculate your financial freedom.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;6:36—Why using Syndicated Deal Analyzer can help you with your investment deal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;7:49—Exploring deals in other parts of the country.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;8:41—How to spot a good deal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;10:28—The story of Michael’s first deal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;12:05—To wholesale or not to wholesale.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;13:28—What investors can learn at one of Michael’s seminars.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;15:43—A word from or sponsors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;18:42—What makes Michael’s training system different.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;20:19—The hardest thing, in Michael’s opinion, about jumping into the investment business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;22:20—Creating financial freedom in multi-family property investing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;24:50—The three ways you can participate in an investment deal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;27:14—Where you can buy Michael’s book: “Financial Freedom With Real Estate Investing.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;27:47—Where Michael finds his inspiration and where you can too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;30:24—Concluding thoughts and the importance of taking action.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I want to thank Michael for joining me. If you need to reach out to him, you can visit his website at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.themichaelblank.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;www.themichaelblank.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As always, if you have any questions for me or there’s anything else I can help you with, feel free to give me a call or shoot me an email. I’d love to help you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 14:29:48 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/retire-in-3-to-5-years-by-investing-in-multi-family-property.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/retire-in-3-to-5-years-by-investing-in-multi-family-property.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Talking Real Estate Investment Mistakes with Rod Khleif</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/U0OCoW2Ga8A?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Welcome back to another exciting episode of “Real Estate Raw.” Today I have the privilege of being joined by a fantastic real estate mind. Rod Khleif is a passionate real estate investor who has been a mentor to me in this business. He joined us to talk about a number of topics, including the real estate market, his charitable works, and of course, real estate investment. &lt;strong&gt;Here’s an outline of our conversation, with timestamps so that you can skip ahead to the sections(s) that interest you the most:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1:45- Mistakes investors can make by rushing into their first deal and how to fix them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4:30- Why investors shouldn’t ignore secondary and tertiary towns.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;7:20- Why Rod believes so many investors give up too early.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;13:15- The importance of networking with brokers for multi-family property investors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;15:40- Why buying a property in a one-employer town could lead to tragedy for an investor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;22:00- Rod’s thoughts on LoopNet and the deals you may be able to find there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;24:55- Why Rod believes seller financing is a great investment strategy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;28:10- Good buy criteria for new investors who want to own a multi-family property.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;31:30- Why analysis paralysis is a death sentence in this business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks again to Rod for joining me. His knowledge and experience were invaluable to me in my career and I hope he can help you in your career as well. If you have any questions for Rod, feel free to reach out to him at his website or via his email, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:info@RodKhleif.com&quot;&gt;info@RodKhleif.com&lt;/a&gt;. If you have any other questions for me, don’t hesitate to reach out and give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 11:42:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/talking-real-estate-investment-mistakes-with-rod-khleif.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/talking-real-estate-investment-mistakes-with-rod-khleif.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Real Estate Raw Featuring Kim Lisa Taylor</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/AeEJT5H0bdA?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Welcome back to another episode of “Real Estate Raw”. Today I am joined by a very special guest, Kim Lisa Taylor. I’ve watched her real estate investment career explode from the beginning, and I’m honored and privileged to have her join us. &lt;strong&gt;Here’s a quick outline of our conversation, with timestamps so that you can skip ahead to the part(s) that interest you most&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1:15- Kim gives us a rundown of who she is and what she does.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2:20- What are securities in the real estate investment world and how can you use them to your advantage?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3:45- Kim’s expert advice for someone who has an investment property in mind but doesn’t have the money lined up to buy it yet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;6:15- Kim’s thoughts on the common saying “Find a deal and you’ll find the money.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;10:50- What is the “3-touch rule” and is it a worthwhile strategy?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;12:45- Kim’s exemption advice for international investors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;14:30- How does “Reg A” work?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;17:30- The quality vs. quantity argument in real estate investing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;18:30- What a family office is and how it operates as an investment business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;21:05- Kim’s advice for a brand-new real estate investor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;25:20- Last words from Kim about how she can help you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Real estate investing isn’t something you can do alone.%20http://localhost:4000/real-estate-raw-featuring-kim-lisa-taylor.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Real estate investing isn’t something you can do alone.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Real estate investment isn’t something you can do alone. If you have any questions for me or you’d like some further advice, don’t hesitate to reach out and give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 14:28:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/real-estate-raw-featuring-kim-lisa-taylor.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/real-estate-raw-featuring-kim-lisa-taylor.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Real Estate Raw: Kaaren Hall</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/azLd97Co7so?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Welcome to another episode of “Real Estate Raw.” Today I am excited to be joined by the amazing Kaaren Hall, who shared some invaluable tips with me about self-directed IRAs, which is one of her many specialties. &lt;strong&gt;Here’s an outline of our discussion, with timestamps so that you can skip ahead to the section(s) that interest you the most:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1:15- A closer look at Kaaren’s business and how it helps her clients create wealth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3:15- Kaaren’s path to real estate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4:30- One real estate investment strategy that Kaaren swears by.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;6:50- How a self-directed IRA is different than a SEP IRA.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;9:00- The minimum fees and investments it takes to get involved with Kaaren and her investments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;13:30- How crowdfunding fits into Kaaren’s investment products.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;15:40- Kaaren’s thoughts on today’s market.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;16:30- How Kaaren and her company set themselves apart from the competition.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;18:20- Why so many of Kaaren’s clients are making their investments in Florida.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;23:45- The only thing that someone needs to start a retirement plan for their child.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;26:30- Where Kaaren recommends you go to learn more about her business and what she does.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;27:45- Final thoughts and advice from Kaaren.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions for me, don’t hesitate to give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2018 14:55:24 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/real-estate-raw-kaaren-hall.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/real-estate-raw-kaaren-hall.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
