<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:itunesu="http://www.itunesu.com/feed" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>The Real Estate Raw Show with Joe Mendoza</title>
    <link>http://localhost:4000</link>
    <atom10:link xmlns:atom10="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="http://localhost:4000"/>
    <description>If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from Katcam Real Estate - your professional San Diego Real Estate Agents.</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <managingEditor>Joe Mendoza</managingEditor>
    <lastBuildDate>2018-11-01 13:19:57 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <media:copyright>Joe Mendoza</media:copyright>
    <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000/img/podcast.jpg"/>
    <media:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in San Diego, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</media:keywords>
    <media:category scheme="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd">Education</media:category>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:email>joe@joemendoza.com</itunes:email>
      <itunes:name>Joe Mendoza</itunes:name>
    </itunes:owner>
    <itunes:author>Joe Mendoza</itunes:author>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:image href="http://localhost:4000/img/podcast.jpg"/>
    <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in San Diego, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
    <itunes:subtitle>Learn all the tips, tricks and more for buyers and sellers in the San Diego Area Real Estate Market</itunes:subtitle>
    <itunes:summary>If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from Katcam Real Estate - your professional San Diego Real Estate Agents.</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:category text="Education"/>
    
      <item>
        <title>Retire in 3 to 5 Years By Investing in Multi-Family Property</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/retire-in-3-to-5-years-by-investing-in-multi-family-property.html</link>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Joe Mendoza</author>
        <pubDate>2018-10-30 14:29:48 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Joe+Mendoza/San+Diego+Real+Estate-+Investing+Advice+With+Michael+Blank.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Welcome back to another episode of “Real Estate Raw.” Michael Blank is today’s guest, and he’s an absolute guru when it comes to real estate investing–specifically, investing in multi-family property.

In our discussion we cover a variety of important topics, so once again I’ve provided timestamps of the video above so you can jump ahead to the section(s) that interest you the most:

0:49—How Michael got into multi-family property investing.

2:57—How a person can retire in three to five years by investing in multi-family units.

4:45—How to calculate your financial freedom.

6:36—Why using Syndicated Deal Analyzer can help you with your investment deal.

7:49—Exploring deals in other parts of the country.

8:41—How to spot a good deal.

10:28—The story of Michael’s first deal.

12:05—To wholesale or not to wholesale.

13:28—What investors can learn at one of Michael’s seminars.  

15:43—A word from or sponsors.

18:42—What makes Michael’s training system different.

20:19—The hardest thing, in Michael’s opinion, about jumping into the investment business.

22:20—Creating financial freedom in multi-family property investing.

24:50—The three ways you can participate in an investment deal.

27:14—Where you can buy Michael’s book: “Financial Freedom With Real Estate Investing.”

27:47—Where Michael finds his inspiration and where you can too.

30:24—Concluding thoughts and the importance of taking action.

I want to thank Michael for joining me. If you need to reach out to him, you can visit his website at www.themichaelblank.com.

As always, if you have any questions for me or there’s anything else I can help you with, feel free to give me a call or shoot me an email. I’d love to help you.

 
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Joe+Mendoza/San+Diego+Real+Estate-+Investing+Advice+With+Michael+Blank.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Joe+Mendoza/San+Diego+Real+Estate-+Investing+Advice+With+Michael+Blank.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>On the latest episode of “The Real Estate Raw Show,” Michael Blank explains the tremendous benefits that come from investing in multi-family property.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Joe Mendoza</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>On the latest episode of “The Real Estate Raw Show,” Michael Blank explains the tremendous benefits that come from investing in multi-family property.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in San Diego, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Talking Real Estate Investment Mistakes with Rod Khleif</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/talking-real-estate-investment-mistakes-with-rod-khleif.html</link>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Joe Mendoza</author>
        <pubDate>2018-10-24 11:42:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Joe+Mendoza/2018/San+Diego+Real+Estate-+Rod+Khleif.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Welcome back to another exciting episode of “Real Estate Raw.” Today I have the privilege of being joined by a fantastic real estate mind. Rod Khleif is a passionate real estate investor who has been a mentor to me in this business. He joined us to talk about a number of topics, including the real estate market, his charitable works, and of course, real estate investment. Here’s an outline of our conversation, with timestamps so that you can skip ahead to the sections(s) that interest you the most:

1:45- Mistakes investors can make by rushing into their first deal and how to fix them.

4:30- Why investors shouldn’t ignore secondary and tertiary towns.

7:20- Why Rod believes so many investors give up too early.

13:15- The importance of networking with brokers for multi-family property investors.

15:40- Why buying a property in a one-employer town could lead to tragedy for an investor.

22:00- Rod’s thoughts on LoopNet and the deals you may be able to find there.

24:55- Why Rod believes seller financing is a great investment strategy.

28:10- Good buy criteria for new investors who want to own a multi-family property.

31:30- Why analysis paralysis is a death sentence in this business.

Thanks again to Rod for joining me. His knowledge and experience were invaluable to me in my career and I hope he can help you in your career as well. If you have any questions for Rod, feel free to reach out to him at his website or via his email, info@RodKhleif.com. If you have any other questions for me, don’t hesitate to reach out and give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Joe+Mendoza/2018/San+Diego+Real+Estate-+Rod+Khleif.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Joe+Mendoza/2018/San+Diego+Real+Estate-+Rod+Khleif.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>In the latest episode of “Real Estate Raw,” I was joined by real estate investment expert Rod Khleif. Rod has been a huge mentor to me, and I was excited to talk to him in-depth about how to have success as a real estate investor.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Joe Mendoza</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>In the latest episode of “Real Estate Raw,” I was joined by real estate investment expert Rod Khleif. Rod has been a huge mentor to me, and I was excited to talk to him in-depth about how to have success as a real estate investor.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in San Diego, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Real Estate Raw Featuring Kim Lisa Taylor</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/real-estate-raw-featuring-kim-lisa-taylor.html</link>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Joe Mendoza</author>
        <pubDate>2018-10-10 14:28:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Joe+Mendoza/2018/San+Diego+Real+Estate-+Kim+Lisa+Taylor+(1).mp4</guid>
        <description>

Welcome back to another episode of “Real Estate Raw”. Today I am joined by a very special guest, Kim Lisa Taylor. I’ve watched her real estate investment career explode from the beginning, and I’m honored and privileged to have her join us. Here’s a quick outline of our conversation, with timestamps so that you can skip ahead to the part(s) that interest you most:

1:15- Kim gives us a rundown of who she is and what she does.

2:20- What are securities in the real estate investment world and how can you use them to your advantage?

3:45- Kim’s expert advice for someone who has an investment property in mind but doesn’t have the money lined up to buy it yet.

6:15- Kim’s thoughts on the common saying “Find a deal and you’ll find the money.”

10:50- What is the “3-touch rule” and is it a worthwhile strategy?

12:45- Kim’s exemption advice for international investors.

14:30- How does “Reg A” work?

17:30- The quality vs. quantity argument in real estate investing.

18:30- What a family office is and how it operates as an investment business.

21:05- Kim’s advice for a brand-new real estate investor.

25:20- Last words from Kim about how she can help you.“Real estate investing isn’t something you can do alone.”

Real estate investment isn’t something you can do alone. If you have any questions for me or you’d like some further advice, don’t hesitate to reach out and give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Joe+Mendoza/2018/San+Diego+Real+Estate-+Kim+Lisa+Taylor+(1).mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Joe+Mendoza/2018/San+Diego+Real+Estate-+Kim+Lisa+Taylor+(1).mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Kim Lisa Taylor is not only a successful Attorney, but she’s also as knowledgeable as it gets when it comes to real estate investments. Stay tuned for the latest episode of “Real Estate Raw.”</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Joe Mendoza</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Kim Lisa Taylor is not only a successful Attorney, but she’s also as knowledgeable as it gets when it comes to real estate investments. Stay tuned for the latest episode of “Real Estate Raw.”</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in San Diego, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Real Estate Raw: Kaaren Hall</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/real-estate-raw-kaaren-hall.html</link>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Joe Mendoza</author>
        <pubDate>2018-09-25 14:55:24 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Joe+Mendoza/San+Diego+Real+Estate-+Business+Tips+With+Kaaren+Hall.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Welcome to another episode of “Real Estate Raw.” Today I am excited to be joined by the amazing Kaaren Hall, who shared some invaluable tips with me about self-directed IRAs, which is one of her many specialties. Here’s an outline of our discussion, with timestamps so that you can skip ahead to the section(s) that interest you the most:

1:15- A closer look at Kaaren’s business and how it helps her clients create wealth.

3:15- Kaaren’s path to real estate.

4:30- One real estate investment strategy that Kaaren swears by.

6:50- How a self-directed IRA is different than a SEP IRA.

9:00- The minimum fees and investments it takes to get involved with Kaaren and her investments.

13:30- How crowdfunding fits into Kaaren’s investment products.

15:40- Kaaren’s thoughts on today’s market.

16:30- How Kaaren and her company set themselves apart from the competition.

18:20- Why so many of Kaaren’s clients are making their investments in Florida.

23:45- The only thing that someone needs to start a retirement plan for their child.

26:30- Where Kaaren recommends you go to learn more about her business and what she does.

27:45- Final thoughts and advice from Kaaren.

If you have any questions for me, don’t hesitate to give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.

 
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Joe+Mendoza/San+Diego+Real+Estate-+Business+Tips+With+Kaaren+Hall.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Joe+Mendoza/San+Diego+Real+Estate-+Business+Tips+With+Kaaren+Hall.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>The latest episode of Real Estate Raw is here featuring the amazing Kaaren Hall.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Joe Mendoza</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>The latest episode of Real Estate Raw is here featuring the amazing Kaaren Hall.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in San Diego, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Today on the Real Estate Raw Show: Chris Watters Explains Team Building</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/today-on-the-real-estate-raw-show-chris-watters-explains-team-building.html</link>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Joe Mendoza</author>
        <pubDate>2018-09-14 13:13:42 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Joe+Mendoza/2018/San+Diego+Real+Estate-+An+Outstanding+Talk+With+Chris+Waters.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Today on the Real Estate Raw Show, we’re joined by an amazing special guest: Chris Watters, author of “The Million Dollar Real Estate Team.” After hearing his story, I knew I had to bring him on for an interview. And now, I’m going to share that discussion with all of you.

Cited below for your convenience are timestamps that will direct you to various points in the interview. Feel free to watch the full message or use these timestamps to browse specific topics at your leisure:

0:51 - An introduction to Chris’ book: “The Million Dollar Real Estate Team.”

1:25 - How Chris got to where he is today.

4:10 - What it takes to build a team.

4:50 - How Chris’ book can serve as a blueprint for building a real estate team.

7:50 - How Chris got in front of business owners to grow his monthly mastermind, and what he earns from doing this.

9:47 - Debunking false beliefs about building a real estate team.

10:30 - What Chris looks for in agents he has recruited.

12:36 - How Chris overcame initial failures and became successful in real estate.

14:15 - A word from our sponsors.

17:22 - What drives Chris’ mindset and where he’s drawn inspiration for his success.

20:13 - Why Chris decided to build teams instead of staying solo.

20:52 - How Chris’ other business ventures impacted his success as a real estate professional.

22:19 - A look at Chris’ morning routine and the power of visualizing goals.  

25:33 - How Chris overcomes limiting beliefs and helps his teams do the same.

31:06 - The expectations Chris sets for his teams and how he helps them set goals.

34:50 - What Chris does outside of building teams.

35:04 - The No. 1 piece of advice Chris has to share on being successful in real estate.

If you have any other questions or would more information, feel free to give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.

 
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Joe+Mendoza/2018/San+Diego+Real+Estate-+An+Outstanding+Talk+With+Chris+Waters.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Joe+Mendoza/2018/San+Diego+Real+Estate-+An+Outstanding+Talk+With+Chris+Waters.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Have you ever considered building a real estate team? If so, today’s special guest on the Real Estate Raw Show has some amazing insight on the subject to share.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Joe Mendoza</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Have you ever considered building a real estate team? If so, today’s special guest on the Real Estate Raw Show has some amazing insight on the subject to share.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in San Diego, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>PatLive Can Help Businesses Grow by Allowing Them to Do Less—Here’s How</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/patlive-can-help-businesses-grow-by-allowing-them-to-do-lessheres-how.html</link>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Joe Mendoza</author>
        <pubDate>2018-09-04 11:02:39 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Joe+Mendoza/2018/San+Diego+Real+Estate-+A+Very+Special+Interview+With+PatLive.mp4</guid>
        <description>

I have a very special guest with me today: Richard and Jamie of PatLive. I learned about them over 10 years ago, and it was such a blessing to my business. In showing you this interview, I want to delve into what this virtual reception service is all about.

For your convenience, I’ve attached some timestamps below so you can navigate the conversation at your leisure. Feel free to skip around to any points in the video that interest you in particular.


  1:00—The history of PatLive.
  2:00— “Creme de la Creme”: What it takes to work for PatLive.
  3:50—What is the cost of service?
  4:40—The PatLive guarantee of service.
  5:50—Is PatLive just for Realtors and investors?
  6:20—What does PatLive bring to the table that competitors don’t?
  9:00—The extra level of service PatLive strives for.
  11:00—Who’s all on the PatLive team?
  13:29—Final thoughts from our two guests.


PatLive is there for your callers 24 hours a day. If you ever have any questions about their service or about how to proceed, you can always call. They’d be happy to help.

If you’d like to explore this service option a little further, visit www.joemendoza.com and click on the “Resources” tab, or call my direct-connect line at 1-800-891-2640. Thanks so much to Richard and Jamie for speaking with me and sharing their words of wisdom.

 
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Joe+Mendoza/2018/San+Diego+Real+Estate-+A+Very+Special+Interview+With+PatLive.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Joe+Mendoza/2018/San+Diego+Real+Estate-+A+Very+Special+Interview+With+PatLive.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Listen to my interview with Richard and Jamie of PatLive to learn how their virtual reception service is helping businesses grow.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Joe Mendoza</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Listen to my interview with Richard and Jamie of PatLive to learn how their virtual reception service is helping businesses grow.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in San Diego, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>How Mitch Stephen Became a Mega-Successful Investor, Part II</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-mitch-stephen-became-mega0.html</link>
        
          <category>San Diego Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Joe Mendoza</author>
        <pubDate>2018-08-03 12:04:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Joe+Mendoza/2018/San+Diego+Real+Estate-+Podcast+Stephen+Pt+2.mp4</guid>
        <description>

We’re back with part two of my exclusive interview with mega-successful real estate investor Mitch Stephen.


Want to sell your home? Get a FREE home value report.
Want to buy a home? Search all homes for sale.


On today’s episode of “The Real Estate Raw Show,” I’m excited to conclude our interview with mega-successful real estate investor Mitch Stephen. As I said before, Mitch has bought, owner-financed, and sold over 1,500 homes in his hometown since 1996, and he has plenty more to say about how he was able to do this.

For your convenience, I’ve timestamped the rest of the interview below so that you can jump to whatever topics interest you most:

1:15 - The story of how Mitch wrote his first book.

7:27 - The inspiration behind his message.

9:14 - A CliffsNotes breakdown of all the books Mitch has published and what they can teach you.

15:28 - Books that have changed Mitch’s life and the lessons they taught him.

19:30 - His advice to anyone who thinks they’re stuck in a rut.

22:30 - How he works with sellers and what the benefits of owner financing are.

26:00 - How he automates his business.

29:30 - Why storage units are such a great investment.

Once again, I want to thank Mitch for being on my show, and I hope he can join us again someday to share more stories about how to achieve and maintain his level of success.

“I’M SUPER EXCITED TO SHARE THE SECOND HALF OF THIS INTERVIEW WITH YOU.”

As always, if you have any questions for me regarding buying, selling, or investing in real estate, don’t hesitate to reach out to me. I’d be delighted to help you out.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Joe+Mendoza/2018/San+Diego+Real+Estate-+Podcast+Stephen+Pt+2.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Joe+Mendoza/2018/San+Diego+Real+Estate-+Podcast+Stephen+Pt+2.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

We’re back with part two of my exclusive interview with mega-successful real estate investor Mitch Stephen.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Joe Mendoza</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

We’re back with part two of my exclusive interview with mega-successful real estate investor Mitch Stephen.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in San Diego, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>How Mitch Stephen Became a Mega-Successful Investor</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-mitch-stephen-became-mega.html</link>
        
          <category>San Diego Success Stories</category>
        
        <author>Joe Mendoza</author>
        <pubDate>2018-07-16 12:42:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Joe+Mendoza/San+Diego+Real+Estate-+How+Mitch+Stephen+Became+a+Mega-Successful+Investor.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Mitch Stephen, mega-successful real estate investor, author, and podcast host, is on the phone with me today to discuss how he climbed to the heights he has achieved.


Want to sell your home? Get a FREE home value report.
Want to buy a home? Search all homes for sale.


On today’s episode of “The Real Estate Raw Show,” I’m very excited to introduce our outstanding guest from Texas, Mitch Stephen. Mitch has bought, owner-financed, and sold over 1,500 homes in his hometown since 1996 —not as an agent, but as an investor. He has his own podcast and has written several books, so I’m extremely happy to have him on to discuss how he’s become so successful.

For your convenience, I’ve timestamped the interview below so that you can jump to whatever topics interest you most.

0:40- Retaining one-third of the 1,500 homes Mitch has accumulated.
1:20- Mitch’s path to financial freedom
4:20- What are Mitch’s strengths?
5:20- Explaining owner-financing
8:50- Mitch’s idea of a perfect student
12:25- Mitch’s biggest success stories
15:50- Mitch’s parting advice

I want to thank Mitch so much for being on our show, and I hope he can come back again to explore some other questions about his success. If you would like to get more detailed information about his insight and experiences, visit the following links:

• To buy his book “My Life &amp; 1000 Houses: Failing Forward to Financial Freedom”, or download the first 100 pages for free: https://ub203.isrefer.com/go/book/jm2018/

• To benefit from his online training system “The Art of Owner Finance”, which includes 13 easy-to-digest video/audio modules: https://ub203.isrefer.com/go/497/jm2018/

• To learn a real estate investing technique that blows being a landlord away: https://ub203.isrefer.com/go/oftw/jm2018/

• For tools and training on how to raise private money without fear of failure: https://ub203.isrefer.com/go/pmce/jm2018/

If you have any questions for me regarding buying, selling, or investing in real estate, don’t hesitate to reach out to me. I’d be delighted to help you out.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Joe+Mendoza/San+Diego+Real+Estate-+How+Mitch+Stephen+Became+a+Mega-Successful+Investor.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Joe+Mendoza/San+Diego+Real+Estate-+How+Mitch+Stephen+Became+a+Mega-Successful+Investor.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

Mitch Stephen, mega-successful real estate investor, author, and podcast host, is on the phone with me today to discuss how he climbed to the heights he has achieved.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Joe Mendoza</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

Mitch Stephen, mega-successful real estate investor, author, and podcast host, is on the phone with me today to discuss how he climbed to the heights he has achieved.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in San Diego, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>A Great Conversation With an Amazing General Contractor</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/a-great-conversation-with-amazing.html</link>
        
          <category>San Diego Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Joe Mendoza</author>
        <pubDate>2018-06-29 14:15:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Joe+Mendoza/San+Diego+Real+Estate-+A+Great+Conversation+With+an+Amazing+General+Contractor.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Darrin Brightmon is a fantastic general contractor here in San Diego. We had a great conversation about he does and how he helps people every day.


Want to sell your home? Get a FREE home value report.
Want to buy a home? Search all homes for sale.


Welcome to another edition of the “Real Estate Raw Show.” Today I have a very special guest, Darrin Brightmon. He’s a former star running back for UNLV, a colonel in the Army Reserves, and a fantastic general contractor with a great company, BDG Builders. I sat down with him to talk about the business, what he does, and how he helps people like myself and my clients on a daily basis. Here’s an outline of our discussion, with timestamps so that you can skip around to the topics that interest you most:

1:30- How Darrin got into the general contracting business.

3:00- The different licenses in the contracting world and the licenses that Darrin has himself.

5:40- The importance of bonds when hiring a contractor like Darrin and how they protect the consumer.

7:15- The dangers of hiring unlicensed or unbonded contractors to save a bit of money.

9:15- A rundown of a few of the projects Darrin is working on in San Diego right now.

“DARRIN WORKS WITH SAN DIEGO PROPERTY OWNERS EVERY SINGLE DAY.”

11:20- The difference between residential and commercial contracting work.

12:00- Why hiring Darrin and BDG Builders to help build your new home is such a great idea.

If you have any questions for Darrin about how he can help you, don’t hesitate to reach out and give him a call at (858) 354-1041 or head on over to www.BDGBuilders.com.

If you have any mortgage-related questions or needs, don’t forget about our friend Akshay Patel at Easy Fundings Home Loans. You can reach him at (858) 207-8436.

Finally, if you have any questions regarding real estate, the market, or anything else, you can always reach out and give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Joe+Mendoza/San+Diego+Real+Estate-+A+Great+Conversation+With+an+Amazing+General+Contractor.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Joe+Mendoza/San+Diego+Real+Estate-+A+Great+Conversation+With+an+Amazing+General+Contractor.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

Darrin Brightmon is a fantastic general contractor here in San Diego. We had a great conversation about he does and how he helps people every day.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Joe Mendoza</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

Darrin Brightmon is a fantastic general contractor here in San Diego. We had a great conversation about he does and how he helps people every day.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in San Diego, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>An Interview With One of the Hardest-Working Lenders Around</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/an-interview-with-one-of-hardest.html</link>
        
          <category>San Diego Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Joe Mendoza</author>
        <pubDate>2018-06-18 12:44:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Joe+Mendoza/San+Diego+Real+Estate-+An+Interview+With+One+of+the+Hardest-Working+Lenders+Around.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Akshay Patel is not just a mortgage lender, he’s an undeniable force. Here’s what makes him so special.


Want to sell your home? Get a FREE home value report.
Want to buy a home? Search all homes for sale.


I’m so excited to be joined by a special guest today. He’s super unique, super ambitious, and I’m excited to be sharing the stage with him today. His name is Akshay Patel and he is an absolutely fantastic mortgage lender here in San Diego.

I recently had a VA buyer who wasn’t able to get him qualified with other lenders. Once they went to Akshay, he was able to get the buyer qualified. Here’s why.

One big reason why Akshay is so successful is that he focuses on solutions, not problems. Instead of just saying no or pushing things to the side if there isn’t an easy fix, he works to find solutions to all of our clients’ problems. He’s actually been able to get seven deals done this year that other lenders weren’t able to get done first. Whether it’s a long-term plan or a short-term one, if there’s a solution, Akshay is going to find it.

“IF THERE’S A SOLUTION, AKSHAY IS GOING TO FIND IT.”

There are no days off for Akshay, and that’s because he’s passionate about getting homebuyers qualified to purchase homes. He’s persistent, he never gives up, and he goes the extra mile for everyone he works with. He wasn’t hustling for our clients just because he was a friend, he was hustling because he is all about his business. He wants to help bring us to the next level, and we want to do the same for him. It’s been a very fruitful partnership thus far.

The big banks generally make our clients jump through so many hoops, a lot of times they end up just wanting to give up. I recently had a client who was fed up with the big banks and trying to do a 1031 exchange, so I set him up with Akshay and was able to get a solution figured out in just a quick, 20-minute phone call. Even if clients get turned down by other lenders, Akshay never takes no for an answer.

If you’re not sure whether or not that you can qualify to buy a home, you should get in touch with Akshay first. You can give him a call at (858) 207-8436. If you have any other questions about real estate in the meantime, don’t hesitate to give us a call or send us an email. We look forward to working with you soon.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Joe+Mendoza/San+Diego+Real+Estate-+An+Interview+With+One+of+the+Hardest-Working+Lenders+Around.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Joe+Mendoza/San+Diego+Real+Estate-+An+Interview+With+One+of+the+Hardest-Working+Lenders+Around.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

Akshay Patel is not just a mortgage lender, he’s an undeniable force. Here’s what makes him so special.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Joe Mendoza</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

Akshay Patel is not just a mortgage lender, he’s an undeniable force. Here’s what makes him so special.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in San Diego, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>A Story of Investing Success</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/a-story-of-investing-success.html</link>
        
          <category>San Diego Success Stories</category>
        
        <author>Joe Mendoza</author>
        <pubDate>2018-05-23 12:19:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Joe+Mendoza/San+Diego+Real+Estate-+A+Story+of+Investing+Success.mp4</guid>
        <description>

My special guest, Hector Padilla, is here today to share his story about how he went from washing dishes to being a multimillionaire real estate investor.


Want to sell your home? Get a FREE home value report.
Want to buy a home? Search all homes for sale.


Hector Padilla, my guest today is a great friend of mine in the multifamily commercial investing business. Since I met him in 2004, I have watched him accumulate massive amounts of property.

Today I want to share some of his story and discuss how he got from washing dishes to accumulating over $86 million worth of property. I have provided timestamps for you below so that you can jump to whatever topics you like throughout the video above.

• 1:05 - Hectors humble beginnings as a dishwasher.

• 2:20 - The drive to succeed is driven by your circle of influence.

• 4:20 - The value of hiring a coach: exponential growth.

• 7:40 - Think about your ideal lifestyle; how much will it cost you?

• 11:55 - Making lots of money is not the same thing as creating wealth.

• 13:35 - Dont hold yourself back by assuming that you dont need to grow.

• 15:30 - Focus on what youre good at. If real estate isnt your skill, consider partnering with an acquisition firm in a joint venture.

• 17:00 - If you are thinking about making a sudden career change: read Pivot by Adam Markel.

• 18:50 - Details about Hectors free webinar wherein he tells more of his story and how he works with funding partners and private investors to find deals.

• 20:20 - Rude awakenings as motivation.

• 22:00 - Dont give in to the victim mentality. Excuses are not crutches.

• 25:00 - Success in real estate and wealth creation is hard work.

• 26:35 -  If its meant to be, its up to me.

I really appreciate the time Hector took to have this discussion with me and the insight to success that his story provides. If you have any questions about buying, selling, or investing in real estate, you are absolutely encouraged to reach out to us. We can discuss your goals and talk about what we can bring to the table in order to make them happen.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Joe+Mendoza/San+Diego+Real+Estate-+A+Story+of+Investing+Success.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Joe+Mendoza/San+Diego+Real+Estate-+A+Story+of+Investing+Success.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

My special guest, Hector Padilla, is here today to share his story about how he went from washing dishes to being a multimillionaire real estate investor.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Joe Mendoza</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

My special guest, Hector Padilla, is here today to share his story about how he went from washing dishes to being a multimillionaire real estate investor.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in San Diego, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
    <copyright>Joe Mendoza</copyright>
    <media:credit role="author">Joe Mendoza</media:credit>
    <media:rating>nonadult</media:rating>
    <media:description type="plain">If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from Katcam Real Estate - your professional San Diego Real Estate Agents.</media:description>
  </channel>
</rss>
